Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2012
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Haupt, Irene
1 DVD (132 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 132 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo Festival 2012 at the University at Buffalo, including guest composers Fred Lerdahl, Steven Stucky, and Robert Beaser.
All files in the collection renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Renamed files stored with the collection on a separate DVD.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2012.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2012 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012 contains 132 digital images of participants in the festival for 2012. The list of musicians includes David Felder, Brad Lubman, Jean Kopperud, Barry Crawford, Roberto Fabbriciani, Tom Kolor, JoAnn Falletta, Elliot Fisk, Steven Stucky, Fred Lerdahl, James Baker, Robert Beaser, Dan Bassin, Scott Voyles, the New York New Music Ensemble, Ensemble Interface, Signal Ensemble, and Jon Nelson and the Genkin Philharmonic.
Arrangement
One series arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Student composer David Rappenecker with his piece Emergence for percussion quartet at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_001)
- Percussionists Michelle Purdy, C.W. Dunbar, and Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_002)
- Percussionist Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble rehearsing student composer David Rappenecker's work Emergence at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_003)
- Members of the UB Percussion Ensemble rehearsing student composer David Rappenecker's work Emergence at June in Buffalo 2012. Percussionists left to right: Jason Bauers, Robert Fullex, C.W. Dunbar, and Michelle Purdy, 2012-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_004)
- Conductor Dan Bassin with percussionists Michelle Purdy, C.W. Dunbar, Robert Fullex, and Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble and student composer David Rappenecker at a rehearsal of Rappenecker's work Emergence at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_005)
- Senior faculty composer Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_006)
- Unidentified student composer at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_007)
- Horn player Adam Unsworth of Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing composer David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_008)
- Trombonist Benjamin Herrington of Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing composer David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_009)
- Trombonist Benjamin Herrington and tubist Raymond Stewart of Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing composer David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_010)
- Trumpet player Jon Nelson and horn player Adam Unsworth of Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing composer David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_011)
- Trumpet player Tim Leopold, trombonist Benjamin Herrington, and tubist Raymond Stewart of Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing composer David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_012)
- Student composers Ruben Naeff, Duncan Schouten, and Zane Merritt at June in Buffalo 2012., 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_013)
- Student composers Nissim Schaul, Juan Colon Hernandez, Jonghee Kang, Yeung-Ping Chen, and Mark Popeney at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_014)
- Composer David Felder speaking at June in Buffalo 2012, 2009-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_015)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_016)
- Horn player Adam Unsworth, trumpet player Mike Gurfield, and trombonist Benjamin Herrington of Signal in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_017)
- Clarinetist Bill Kalinkos and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky of Signal in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_018)
- Conductor Brad Lubman rehearsing with Signal members, flutist Kelli Kathman, oboist Jackie Leclair, clarinetist Bill Kalinkos, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, violinist Courtney Orlando, horn player Adam Unsworth, trumpet player Mike Gurfield, trombonist Benjamin Herrington, pianist David Friend, and percussionist Bill Solomon at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_019)
- Percussionist Bill Solomon of Signal in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_020)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and percussionist Michael Compitello of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_021)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and percussionist Michael Compitello of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_022)
- Pianist Anna D'Errico of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_023)
- Student composer David Rappenecker and conductor Dan Bassin at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_024)
- Violinist Yuki Numata, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, clarinetist Jean Kopperud, and pianist Steve Beck rehearsing student composer Dimitar Pentchev's work 1:05 at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_025)
- Score of student composer Duncan Schouten's work Of Those Beneath for percussion quartet at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_026)
- Student composer Duncan Schouten with percussionists Jason Bauers, Michelle Purdy, John Bacon, and Tom Kolor in a rehearsal of Schouten's work Of Those Beneath for percussion quartet at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_027)
- Student composer Duncan Schouten and conductor Tom Kolor in a rehearsal of Schouten's work Of Those Beneath at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_028)
- Percussionist John Bacon in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_029)
- Composer Steven Stucky leads a masterclass with student composers Colin Labadie, Tyler Capp, Zane Merritt, Andres Carrizo, Eun Young Lee, and David Rappenecker at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_030)
- Composer Steven Stucky leads a masterclass with student composers Colin Labadie, Tyler Capp, Zane Merritt, Andres Carrizo, Eun Young Lee, and David Rappenecker at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_031)
- Composer David Felder leads a masterclass with student composers at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_032)
- Composer David Felder leads a masterclass with student composers at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_033)
- Conductor Tom Kolor with student composer Jonathan Kolm in a rehearsal of Kolm's work Cantogo at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_034)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_035)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_036)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_037)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_038)
- Flutist Roberto Fabbriciani rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_039)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directs percussionists Liz Holland, Robert Fullex, Jason Bauers, and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_040)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directs percussionists Michelle Purdy, Robert Fullex, Jason Bauers, and Liz Holland of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_041)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directs percussionists Robert Fullex, Michelle Purdy, Liz Holland, and Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_042)
- Percussionists Robert Fullex and Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_043)
- Percussionists Jason Bauers and Robert Fullex UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_044)
- Conductor Dan Bassin with percussionists Jason Bauers, Robert Fullex, C.W. Dunbar, and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_045)
- Conductor Dan Bassin directs percussionists Jason Bauers, Robert Fullex, C.W. Dunbar, and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_046)
- Conductor Dan Bassin directs percussionists Jason Bauers, Robert Fullex, C.W. Dunbar, and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance of student composer David Rappenecker's work Emergence at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_047)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directs percussionists Michelle Purdy, John Bacon, Jason Bauers, and Liz Holland of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_048)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directs percussionists Michelle Purdy, John Bacon, Jason Bauers, and Liz Holland of the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_049)
- Composers Fred Lerdahl and Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_050)
- Composer Robert Beaser at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_051)
- Composer Steven Stucky in a master class with student composers at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_052)
- Composer David Felder leads a master class with student composers Jacob Gotlib and Matthew Schreibeis at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_053)
- Senior faculty composers David Felder, Robert Beaser, Fred Lerdahl, and Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_054)
- Flutist Barry Crawford performing David Felder's work November Sky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_055)
- Flutist Barry Crawford performing David Felder's work November Sky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_056)
- Flutist Barry Crawford performing David Felder's work November Sky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_057)
- Composer David Felder with flutist Barry Crawford after a performance of Felder's work November Sky at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_058)
- Percussionists Robert Fullex, Jason Bauers, Liz Holland, and C.W. Dunbar of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Julia Wolfe's work Dark Full Ride at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_059)
- Trumpet players Jon Nelson and Tim Leopold, horn player Adam Unsworth, trombonist Benjamin Herrington, and tubist Raymond Stewart of Slee Sinfonietta performing David Felder's work Canzone XXXI at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_060)
- Percussionists Liz Holland and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_061)
- Percussionists Robert Fullex, Liz Holland, and Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_062)
- Percussionists Melanie Voytovich and C.W. Dunbar of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_063)
- Percussionist Jason Bauers of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_064)
- Conductor Tom Kolor directing the UB Percussion Ensemble in a performance of Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_065)
- Percussionist Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_066)
- Percussionist Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_067)
- Percussionist Michelle Purdy of the UB Percussion Ensemble performing Iannis Xenakis's work Persephassa at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_068)
- Composer David Felder with UB faculty members Bruce Jackson and Diane Christian at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_069)
- Composer David Felder with student composers Jonathan Kolm and Jonghee Kang at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_070)
- Flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, and percussionists Michael Compitello and Bill Solomon of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_071)
- Conductor Scott Voyles and pianist Anna D'Errico of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_072)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with composer Fred Lerdahl at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_073)
- Conductor Scott Voyles in a rehearsal with violoncellist Christophe Mathias, violinist Veronique Mathieu, and clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky of Ensemble Interface at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_074)
- Conductor Scott Voyles of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_075)
- Conductor Scott Voyles of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_076)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with violoncellist Christophe Mathias and violinist Veronique Mathieu of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_077)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with violoncellist Christophe Mathias and violinist Veronique Mathieu of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_078)
- Conductor Scott Voyles of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_079)
- Conductor Scott Voyles of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_080)
- Pianist Anna D'Errico of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_081)
- Flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshanksy, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, violinist Veronique Mathieu, and pianist Anna D'Errico of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_082)
- Conductor James Baker with violinist Curtis Macomber, violoncellist Chris Finkel, percussionist Tom Kolor, and pianist Stephen Gosling of the New York New Music Ensemble performing student composer Colin Labadie's work Quartet at June in Buffalo 2012, 2009-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_083)
- Pianist Stephen Gosling, violinist Curtis Macomber, and clarinetist Jean Kopperud of the New York New Music Ensemble performing student composer Matthew Schreibeis's work In Search of Planet X at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_084)
- Conductor James Baker directs a performance of student composer Davide Ianni's work Transients with flutist Jayn Rosenfeld, violoncellist Chris Finckel, and clarinetist Jean Kopperud of the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_085)
- Conductor Scott Voyles directs a performance of Morton Feldman's work For Frank O'Hara with pianist Anna D'Errico, violinist Veronique Mathieu, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, and percussionist Michael Compitello of Ensemble Interface at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_086)
- Conductor Scott Voyles directs Ensemble Interface in a performance of Beat Furrer's work Gaspra at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Anna D'Errico, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, percussionist Bill Solomon, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, and flutist Bettina Danielle Berger., 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_087)
- Conductor Scott Voyles directs Ensemble Interface in a performance of Beat Furrer's work Gaspra at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Anna D'Errico, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, percussionist Bill Solomon, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, and flutist Bettina Danielle Berger., 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_088)
- Conductor Scott Voyles directs Ensemble Interface in a performance of Louis Andriessen's work Zilver at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers: pianist Anna D'Errico, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, and percussionists Bill Solomon and Michael Compitello., 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_089)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with members of Ensemble Interface after a performance at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Anna D'Errico, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violoncellist Christophe Mathias; back row: percussionists Bill Solomon and Michael Compitello, 6/6/2012, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_090)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with members of Ensemble Interface after a performance at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: percussionists Bill Solomon and Michael Compitello, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, violinist Veronique Mathieu, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and pianist Anna D'Errico., 2012-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_091)
- Flutist Jayn Rosenfeld and pianist Stephen Gosling of the New York New Music Ensemble with composer Robert Beaser at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_092)
- Members of Ensemble Interface: violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, harpist Kristen Moss Theriault, and percussionist Michael Compitello in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_093)